Okay, let's start with
hunger. Let's
see if you're still following. I've been
teaching for eight years and I
promise to finish this book. It's very long,
about a thousand pages, and I think it's
the greatest book that has ever been
written. Hunger and finishing the steps
on the path to deity,
or Buddha for dummies, that's what it does. The
things will
enlighten you. You don't have to think about
it. It's a list of the things you
have to do and in the end they will
enlighten you. That's hunger.
Who can tell me how hunger
relates to the five themes and the
four schools we saw yesterday? How does the
law course relate to the Am
Ring
Peters course?
Ah, so
if you have time and you're very
passionate,
do the gadget course. If you have time
and you're very passionate about the
gas course, it's much deeper, very deep.
If you don't have time, if you're a
farmer in Tibet, then once a
month or every two months you go with a lama and
do hunger. So that's the
relationship. Hunger has all the
basic information of the course, but
not as detailed as we're going to
see it today and tomorrow. Not in as much detail,
but it's a very good, solid summary
of the whole thing.  cake a course of streets I already
took the course of taking the course of
going to the second turn of the wheel
and the third turn of the wheel is to
use it in a way that you can use it
as in it if there are if you have students
you can do the whole law course and they don't
have time then do the hunger with
them now a question for 0 dollars
because they already have the bad habit of that
money especially someone what would be
a short and great wire that you
can teach people the three
main paths which is
the three main paths but
because a baby teacher would start with that
in the 18 courses in case the student
quits they already have all the hunger in the
first course
so it's not a very bad strategy
so we're going to do 2 more wires this
week in the afternoon
you're going to learn how to teach the
shortest hunger in history of 14 verses 6
say the cndh are the cndh are the three
the three main teachings of
Buddhism it's the shortest river plan there is
then and in the morning you're going to be the
longest wire one of the longest there is so
we're going to do the wire of
Pavón Carring Porsche, the great
Landrin, who wrote the commentary
for the afternoon landing, and Pavón
Carim Porsche is the same person. In the
morning, well, study
his thousand-page book. In the afternoon, you're going
to study his two-page book. Game
at this pace in time.
And the other one was eating with some
people, with my old lady, whose little son
visited, and they said, "What is your
favorite book?" And I said, "The Hunger: The
Gift of Liberation in Your Hands,"
and I think it's the greatest book on
this planet. So we're going to go
through this, we're going to
savor it
without rushing, we're going to savor this
Landrin, and it's going to take us
almost all of us, more like 15 years.
We're halfway through, and I promise you a dessert. I
promised you a dessert. This is "The Hunger,"
which is one of the longest in
history. It doesn't have a very large section
called Viviana. It's not Vipassana. I don't know
who wrote it; I always suspected
things when they misspelled the
leader's name.
Before the final section of "The
Hunger," it's about how to develop meditation.
You see, emptiness directly,
always the last section of hunger, that's it. So,
Rinpoche, they say,
years ago, decided not to focus on this, didn't
make it very big, and why?
Because he already jumped to it, he already did it in
his land ring, Chemo, it's like 300
pages of it,
and so I promised you for dessert that it's
going to take another 8 years, so
we're going to be here for a while. Oh,
and so, that's our plan, that's our
strategy, we're not halfway there.
Very well, here we go.
Third,
yes, I
'm gay,
what is it? I'm
going to put the text in so that you have
a very good seed in case you want to be
translators.
I cried the air,
and she helps
manage it.
The translators from China are like 40, and
we have like 20 in heat. It's not just to
put seeds in your mind word
by word, and I'm going to enjoy the text
very slowly, and I don't care if you get
bored or don't want to study, even if you don't
want to study Tibetan.
I'm fine, I'm Chavez, in the
next life, to be
on Joyce's translation team.
So, he's quoting two, what theme
is thought?  Sure, and what number is
3? So, I'm quoting the
mother of thought, which is by
Chandra Sirte.
The other one I want to give myself here tells me,
but there's more. I'm
going to the dollar
now. The Wheel of Life has two
links. Two of them are karma, which is
2010.
Give people a chance, all
12 of the 12.
So, what is the second link?
Is the team? Someone is making comics,
or someone is making pots. So,
in the Wheel of Life, he's
making pots.
So, in the last few months, I already have a
garden, and this is the time to plant things.
We just planted things: melons,
watermelons. And when you put the seeds
in the ground, that's called karma.
Fresh watermelons.
Then it cooks, and everything cooks. It gets
water, sun, heat, fertilizer. And
then link number 10, which is a
person, a pregnant woman, the seed
is reaching,
like in August, the first one. The second is
the seed in March, and the day is
the seed in something that, in August, has already
had rain and light and fertilizer.
So, this is very clear in my mind,
but it's very difficult to explain when...
You put the seed in the ground, there are
many people,
there's a table in the factory, and everyone
is asleep. Then when you put
water on it, which is impossible if the water touches the
hollow seed,
then they wake up in Haiti, in white,
and it's like October in the jewelry business,
and the one that comes at Christmas is coming.
Then 60% of the diamonds are
sold here, then everyone goes
crazy, and then inside the seed,
all the workers are there. Now
we have to get this watermelon out, the sand,
everyone goes crazy
from the seed. I'm ready to open it, I
know it's going to come out,
third school, the third, second
school, third temple.
Then suddenly they start talking
outside about time,
which makes two go to 10 of a
watermelon seed: sunlight, the sun, the
water, the fertilizer, but in your
mind, that anesthetic that makes the
seed go from 2 to 10 in the
coffee meditation
for good deeds, good
seeds, and for bad seeds. And
listen to these very deep implants,
good seeds feeling, you want them to
create until you are pregnant and a
baby like me who has to go, and
then rejoice a lot before
you fall asleep.  Think about all the
good things you did, and then they'll
grow and grow. That awakens
the whole factory. Rejoicing awakens the
factory
of a good seed, but what awakens
the factory of a bad seed?
Good answer, very interesting. What is
the opposite of coffee meditation? They already
say Waker to Patzi, the way a
bad seed gets pregnant. This Nadal
extends is not understanding, which
is very interesting. What makes
bad seeds grow
faster is not understanding how they work.
Here,
the opposite of rejoicing in serious things is what
Bosch and Jerte put, that anger. But it's
not just people's misunderstanding.
The waters of Orihuela, theoretical and
Carlos's bed, outside
you have, it would be much better
or bad karma is good karma.
In my three-year retreat, I ate a
package of ice cream. It's the only one
I ate in three years, and Kate, so there's
balance. There's one more part of the ice cream, yes, they run out. So that's
the bad part, it's
the bad seed
that makes the ice cream run out. It's that I did
n't understand the ice cream, I wanted it but I didn't
I understood, and if I had understood and
given half
so that those who were left caring for me could enjoy it,
then I would have had
more. But my desire
took hold of me,
and it's because not understanding karma makes
the seed grow.
Interestingly, Dharma Kirdi talks
about what makes the seed
fatten,
and then he talks about links 8 and 9 without
tearing down plazas and gardens. Understanding
cleared, and time
is to have a misunderstanding before
dying, so the seeds become so strong
that their name is reborn. So
from here it says if you want to
stop the seed from growing,
okay, do the
four powers, which destroy the
negative seeds. And you don't just put them in the
freezer and then lock them
so they never open. You can't destroy a
negative seed like that. Why?
Because there is justice in the universe.
Those who hurt people should be the ones who help people.
Those who help people
should be helped. Now you can
magically say, "All your
sins are resolved, they're gone."
Doing this always has gravity,
Prince, it's like Soy Drama Critics, it's Paris.
So here it tells you how to...
You have a bad seed like it extinguishes
a bad one, sure how do you make
the boys fall asleep again in the
legation? They fall, image, text, law, they feel
in my hands
and it won't be able to give new results and
you close the factory of the bad seed, okay,
the whole people who come for rain
and he
from the glass of this Sunday, have
you already decided, man,
or not? So
if you think that he's not going
to do it again, the seed would be
weak like a pill the next day
after you do something bad, if
you decide that you're not going to do it again,
then kill the power, it's the power of
which 7, 6, 1
if you want to see
[Music]
the bedbug that they check, I felt good,
who
33,
the material cause of the tree and the
conditions like water and fertilizers,
225 dollars for Word
and a half,
the conditions and the conditions, not the
seed is here, it's talking about how to
kill,
don't go after the seed,
after the conditions,
very bad work,
the sun,
Sanchis, that you take away the seed, but
you took away the conditions from Michetti,
so, weapon that tells you something like that
and provides the support of the negative, it
still stands, the seed is going to grow
The factory attraction and then know
technically and technically it's the name of the
water in the city is like the
initial desire and number 9
spit out the tongue the advanced desire
then the 8 technically iris the wheel
of life is called the desire begins
if you go to another life
for you
I am on the third wheel
I must leave things what he is saying is what is
the initial desire and this advanced one and
that it opens in the eleven
the answer is no
desire is not the problem what is the
problem
Augustine not understand
but because in the teaching of the days
the link
have sunlight the two suns
is advanced because we find the desire
is part of the answer
that proves is the teaching of the wheel and
the number of the wheel
was in the period of lists and had
not yet reached the emptiness of the
teaching of the wheel is very eager for the
first presentation of the wheel that
life
the different ideas of the schools the
schools
they are also correct not only one
teaches something that is not correct to
push the student a little higher
is to help him but it is not real
then on this side although he is
talking to the farmers he tells them desires
cause the bad seed that  The bad
deed there opens so you can cut
that light, that illusion, single
universal seed is an introduction to the topic of
until it offers money, it's a
perfect answer if you're going to bring, if you
want to talk,
talk about how they killed the seeds
so that I love you if you don't have them, the
African factory will never open, by then it's
trying to take us to the
next section of hunger in which they were
asked of the mind-disturbing wind,
which is what we were talking about this
morning, okay, how did we get there? Through
school number 2, Dar McCarthy, which
is week, which is deficient in the super
history, it is expected if you study now,
officially, start to suspect that
these facts, there are no teachers from the
lower school,
from the upper school, it's just playing with
your mind, okay, so you
have to look at the sunlight, it
means you have the seed, it's only going to
open if it doesn't by
itself, planting new seeds, it's
not like you don't understand, you plant
seeds
and then the root of the root does
n't go around this rope, it's like
arrows,
I'm nothing more than that, it doesn't mean that and nothing
more, so we must talk, we must
study the equal parts of our
mind all week, we're going to try to
bring to our peaceful mind bring
waste bring society to
purpose it's going to be a depressing week
that has come very well here we go he
says right now he left everything for the wheel
of life are the arrows and then we
must talk about this
question then
ateca for 100 dollars
although the saman hand
someone who knows Tibetan tell me
what it means just one word and if it's
very easy
it's like 10 dollars each letter so sab time's up
the criticism let's
read the board sir of the year call sepa
run run' nam nam khem a touch that
kill you grandtop that so much pp ranking of
ranking plummeting that almost always
sent more and more and xing xing killed walmart
uruguay 77 chile of normal selection that
the child who teaches you
have the class the girls have dictated
is negative
this morning
is very famous and made him a little
wire and made it very easy
this thing that we call place jack
round although more current
disney word this means web this word
means
until after he has seven agents
after he is English is already good
all the time mind ban nam khem a  In fact, he's already
fed up with him staying for tea,
Jr. Besides, there's nothing going on.
The person who has him on their mind is
sending emails. It usually
disturbs me, raising the wind, just like
if you're having a good day,
then critical, thinking about your old
boyfriend, then you lose your balance.
Desire is very crucial in
Buddhist practice, that is, level 10, delight, and in
Taiwan a month ago, Stanley,
and it's the fertilizer for anger in your
mind, it's the imbalances, like if I
was having a good day and suddenly
mentioned the old boyfriend, and then in
English for lifestyle,
that's the 'solo' to McLeish, since they will have
access to their air, their land,
if you want, if you want to study how not to lose your
balance, then even if he comes, I'm not
saying he won't have food, and there's machine
head hunting, herma tour,
tweetdeck, and add something more about being
active,
the mind starts acting like a
horse, which I believe
is the word that integrates when
you think about your old boyfriend on the outside, your
water, that's right, acting hate, you go, it's
acting like crazy. Five minutes
after your ex-boyfriend starts,
I start telling him  Something bad to another
person that makes them like a
wild horse casting and currently be like
a wild horse, damn milk,
that's the function of a cliché, it
has two functions, number one this
imbalance, number two being here,
you can act crazy, being here
Martin is acting like a wild horse,
okay,
so having all kinds of problems
if we continue, critical alarm, what I would
add is to stay here
and it's going to feed your bad seeds, the
negative ones, it's going to be like the sun and water
for your hands, and here I would have read you
this definition, I would have added that it
feeds your negative seeds, it helps them
grow, it's the fertilizer, or that it doesn't
go after the seeds,
cut the fertilizer, remove the
fertilizer, remove the sun, and with a
board on top of the weeds they're going to
die because they need food,
so all your seeds, all this
week we're going to study
how to make them starve, triple,
nobody starves anymore, their bad seeds, it's not that
they're a bad person,
Steven, it's not because they do
n't have food, I
already told you about the potential seeds,
so it's a trick that presents, if there is,
as you say in the index, there, so a
seed, you have, that says when I
ask you if the  Mental seeds with
the ones set
with a complete answer
and lives in the mind,
but it doesn't think, it's not conscious, so it's not,
look, it's not made of
mind, it lives in the mind, even up to the ceiling,
like a potential,
technically a changing thing that
is not physical, it's not physical nor mental, it's just
an intermittency, it's a thing but it's not
mind because it doesn't think, it's not
conscious, that if something is mind and Thomas
Aquinas
should be sucking on objects
for the seeds, but the seeds are like there's
a little guy waiting to
wake up, isn't that really the
answer to the question? It's good, and a
good answer
at this point, let's go to your
meditation book, you have a special
meditation book, and if you don't have it, it's over there
in the box, okay? It
says, "Know-it-all, switch with Wii." This is
a little book for tourists, not for
the week, and guess which is the
first one, which is the image?
And I have seen die. This should be water,
like disturbing the class, not water like a
glass, which the class,
and we already did this meditation this morning,
so in the afternoon, after yoga,
after eating, go home and sleep.
Maybe you want to do this meditation again
because you're supposed to be on retreat,
and even people  In retreat, I take
naps,
I'm reading books, I have to get married, and do
n't expect life to be different
after getting married. There's nothing
special after a ceremony that
will suddenly change you both. Do you understand
why I said that? Just
because you're in retreat doesn't mean you ca
n't see the fact that you're in
retreat. It's not going to change your
daily habits, so go, just flow, go to
yoga like other
stars currently do, and then go to your
meditation class, or if you're in
teacher training, good luck with
your homework.
We made a new word, which is going to
enter the image of an idea, and
these are the ones that are easy to
remember.
According to Chinese characters, they are easy
to remember because in ancient times,
characters like the turtle
resembled things they were meant to
represent. So it's more powerful
in the subconscious guardian, and that's why
the Chinese are
enlisted. I do
n't know,
web, now, not having ideals,
more, I like, I have to, you have to
listen, it's divine,
you have to recognize when the water is being
exalted, it's the name of the game,
my water is being exalted. Now, if you don't
know how to do it, then you're not going to be able to
face it.  So you have to
practice this first meditation, which we're going
to do again tomorrow. And you have to
know what comes next, to know how it
feels when the mind is like
glass. When you're there, don't wait
until you get angry.
When you feel it's really a
little incomplete,
uncomfortable, that's fine. I'm going to sit down,
take a sedative. Don't let it get worse.
You have to be able to recognize
the stages of a baby, of a Clay Shaw
Stadium. Study your own mind; that's the
purpose of meditation. Recognize what it feels like
when your mind is from soft
to a little unbalanced. And the way to
do this this week, during your
meditation,
think of someone who is a problem.
Now is the time because next
week it's going to be someone else.
Get used to seeing how you feel
when you start thinking about
someone you don't like. Get used to
whoever is listening. Recognize how it feels, how it feels, how would you say it feels,
how you feel when you start thinking
about someone you don't like, who you don't get along with.
I would say it's coming on,
or uncomfortable, uncomfortable.
And there it is, between feeling comfortable,
and that's before you say anything, it
starts to feel...  awkward my face look at
my face
that's what it is you should
learn to recognize the thought
behind the face there is a thought
behind the face in your face
so be super sensitive to  That, and
any fool knows when it's wet. You do
n't have to be a Buddhist.
A Buddhist can have the
warning signs if I'm going to get angry or
train without a doubt. This
makes me feel like I can believe what that
guy said the other day. He also
said
you have to be able to recognize that you can
listen to English. I've had two minutes. That
's Buddhist practice. Else,
classical Arabic Buddhism can have an arrow in
two minutes of practice. Better what do I do?
I'm going to get a coffee or something. Change
the ribbon, change the atmosphere. It's
something. I'm going to give you a trick.
If you're in the room and you're going to have a
problem with someone and it's getting
intense,
aim a cup, a plate full of
juice. On purpose, throw the glass
all over the place. It's green juice everywhere,
and it takes 20 minutes to pick it up.
Everyone forgets about stars. Trying it
is very fun.
Angeli forgets about the food that
says it's
also the best for you. It can
get weird, just
like an archer who tries to shoot at the
target but doesn't know what the
target is. If you can't see the target,
how are you going to hit it? You don't know what
English looks like when it's starting. How are you
going to...  To stop, you have to be in
touch with how it feels, taking
five minutes before you get angry.
You have to get in touch with your
own mind
and be able to manage the alarm,
Winnie the Pooh, and love yourself when you
start to slip up, when you're not yet
angry. This mind, if someone
uses it, is an idiot, and you start before I
understand, the question is, it started to
feel uncomfortable. That's
when we're going to shoot the arrow. Do
n't wait until it's very big because you ca
n't stop the anger. Once you're angry, I'm going to
take a stand and
walk. We're going to study the lowest methods
of removing the place. There's one of them:
avoid people. Arrange your life
so that you can't stop
people. But if you don't know what they look like,
then you're not going to be able to shoot them with the
arrow. To shoot the arrow, you have to
know how the GP works and what it looks like
and how to recognize
these. You're going to have a cliché. In fact, it's going to
introduce us to the whole study of
clichés of Depressive Week, and I'm sorry, there's
nothing good.
All week we're going to study clichés.
We're going to be Ecclesia teachers. Wow, they were,
but now you're going to know why.  What a
place, already the first of class, and there are
two divisions of plays, so
now this is the study of 26, the six
main ones, 20 secondary ones, and six
main ones that all have 120 clichés
that you have sometimes in the week of
Hyères, to the week 6 that you have a thousand
times a day, 20 that you have a couple of
times each week, those are the main ones,
the negative ones, the main negative emotions,
and the secondary ones. So they are
very fortunate that two of
our former translators
have translated from this section, one from
Life Weapons and one from Mainoldi, only
then. World translated it in his text of
only then, and it's in the
text of inhabiting more. Then he asked
Stanley
for permission to use translations, and
he says if we're going to give them to him tomorrow or
the next day. It's like 13 pages of
negativity. You can send it to Tim
Howard,
send it to him, like the table,
and you can add it to Style and
Jarque's because a cartload
of 20,
because his thousand-year-old book of thousand-
page weaknesses had it.  That
cutting wasn't teaching crouching, it
was teaching farmers, it cut everything,
but since you guys are dudes, you're gay, you're
babies, so we're going to go through
your six main arrows and then
we're going to go to the twenty arrows of
Stalin's Word, which they so kindly
translated. Our
translation team's strategy is that we have one
translator per school and its sub-
schools, so we're working on
18 texts at the same time from different
schools. Okay, so thank the
translators and see them in the ex-pitcher
and the next image
in your meditation book. It's really about
learning at least those first six
main ones, their names, what they look like, so you
can shoot them.
Learn to recognize them in society, in
your mind. You're probably already
familiar with three of them, and there are
probably three that are there you haven't
seen. So the goal for today
and tomorrow is to learn the main
six and find them in your own mind.
That's real meditation. You have to do it.
No, but I want to meditate
on emptiness. Well, that's fine,
but do this first:
learn to recognize your own clichés
because you've been living with  They've been around for
billions of lifetimes, running through
your mind, and you haven't even
seen them, but your friends have. Because
they have, so
we're going to do meditation
number 2
after learning these 6. 1.
And what we're going to try to do is locate
these six in your mind, jazz, with which you have
n't met some of them, you haven't
recognized them. Okay, very good. Here we go, going out into the
child, not going out into the child, and
part of the text also gives child in
six years, says, teach childhood, children
also go out, children also will be
people, Stanley, bye bye, do
n't believe me?
are the classes, rise, the big ones, the
big six years mean like the
assistants, like the arrows, assistant,
the main six that we have had
many times and all day, and 20 that we
have sometimes, okay, it
fools us here, and I'm going to do two
presentations here, number one, the
main six of the
main negative emotions, and
then I'm going to give you the 20 secondary
emotions, and if I'm in that text, and you
can check it in the Chinese translation, he
left out the 20 here, he promises,
first I'm going to give you this and then,
but he never does, he never does the  20 So we're going to
take it from Stanley de
Wilde.
He's quoting from the Sanskrit, "
listen to the treasure house," which means "
life weapon."
Also, his book is the first one I
showed you yesterday, the first big book. He's
going to the first big book, which is like
the mother book of all the
basic books of the Buddhist faith, which goes on
until 2046.
And here's the verse about
dwelling more. I think it's the first
chapter.
So here's the presentation of the
life weapon, of the six
main negative emotions. So it's the
root of the wheel of life,
and there are 16. And then it says, "This is
a word, life, soul, not to kill." That's
a word for the special
life weapon. For Clesa, it's a different
word. Bring me,
city, that, 50 dollars,
two pieces of this word. I'm going to give you
a hint,
and the slogan,
with the fairy tale,
answers the question. The
question we're talking about is an
alternative name for
negative emotions. It's an alternative name for
Clesa, and it's the name that the life
weapon uses.  That's why our
translation team is divided by
schools, because the word for '
negative emotions at Christmas' is
different from the word for '
negative emotion on the Middle Way' in the
Middle Way school. So then we
specialize our translators.
For example, some are specialized
in the 'life weapon' like Stalin, some in
just 'word,' others in binary
like Shopping
Walkers, Trans Health, subtle James,
which means it's everywhere.
The word for '
life weapon'
is already subtly everywhere. The subtle '
everything'
means that your mind is
infected by all of this, your whole
mind is already there. Everything is similar because my
mind is here, and it's hard to
detect.
You know, cancer, you have cancer and you don't know it,
the sectors haven't been able to find it.
So for the 'life weapon', for
hesitating,
this is the nature of a
negative emotion, and everything has already infected your whole
old mind, and these are
subtle things, they are hard to detect. You can
have an arrow all day and think you're
having a good day. In fact, I just
had a low level of desire for coffee
all day.
So it says that the root of the
suffering of samsara are these six
main kinds
Health hours, which is so subtle and
subtly from all sides, here's the
list, get to know them, you
already know them, but not those who don't
know, you recognize them from Charkh Design
Desire, desire is number one, the
second is the anger area,
then the third is just I
stay monthly, already by McCain
we had a boxer in our gymnastics
of Muhammad Ali who always said I am
the best, I am the best, level was
and then the word but pride in
Buddhism I am the best of the king,
that's number 3, number 4 and Mari
Meza in this misunderstanding from 100
dollars
Aeromexico and agitate
Peter Buck,
verb that transacts, droid
pica if they are thirsty,
but Venerable Field has 100 because he didn't
say ignorance because it's like all
states in that word but it's wrong,
ignorance means not knowing and in
life, Arma specifically says that's
not what causes the problem, it's the
same, it's the misunderstanding, it's normal to
understand things, it's not not being
aware, but it's not understanding well, it's not that you did
n't see your friend, but that you
kissed the wrong guy, that there is a
Big difference. You don't see anyone, or you see the
wrong person. Here we're talking about
kissing the wrong person, which does cause
problems. This is about shopping, and
that's a joke.
The misunderstanding, not ignorance. I don't know
who caused the ignorance. Forget about
that. The FARC was in the water. Number 5, how do you see
the world? How do you see
the world? It's how you see the world,
and that's one of the main ones, one of
the big ones. It's
been a question because you asked two
different ones, Basualdo. Because you say that
number four is misunderstanding, and
number five is like, what is your
worldview? That's not the same thing, and we're not
going to go there, but it's a good
question. If the question came to your mind, you're not
asleep. I didn't
think that number 6,
Hatton,
and then when you teach your students
about the Buddhist concept of peace, you
always have to say
a certain kind of doubt. It's
not a cliché to
ask questions of the teacher, and the
teaching isn't a cliché. To
question the teacher, and the teaching,
that's very healthy. I don't understand
the difference of 345. First you said, and
understanding, then how do you see the
world?  I understand why two different ones.
That's a doubt. It's number six,
but it's not English
because it's healthy. If a student
asks why, repeating number four
and number five means they're still
awake, and that's a very good
thing.
Okay, if they don't ask why you
repeated it
twice, it means they
're asleep or on some level.
Doubt can be a very good thing, and we
can study it.
Let's study what a good doubt is, what a
bad doubt is, what the cliché
of doubt is, and what healthy doubt is.
The neighbor doubts, you're not a debater, and you don't
belong in Tsonga's room. Okay,
which
[Music]
implies that when you're a teacher,
the teacher says, "There you are, teaching
people,
and you have a rigid,
irritating student who keeps asking questions," and
a more or less
trained teacher would be offended.
New questions are written because I don't understand. That's it.
Someone who is more
or less trained would avoid questions, would
avoid speaking, asking questions. A
well-trained teacher is saying, "Very good,
Steven, you're still thinking. You're in
class, you're thinking, and I appreciate it.
Thank you." And I don't have an answer.  I still need
McCain
of Espartales to win because
then the topic of doubt, studying
doubt,
is something very good. What is a good doubt
and what is a bad doubt? What is the one you
're saying here? Well, a bad doubt, a doubt
that hurts you.
So I'm going to give you something in advance in case
we die this afternoon. It's
like being a donkey,
okay,
and thinking like a donkey. The teacher clearly told you
that everything was fine, everything was
fine, and you still don't know. I don't know if I
want to do that. Well, I understand that
meditating for one minute each week is
fine, but if I don't want to do it, I don't know if it will
work. That's because every doubt is bad, okay?
The most Humala-like doubt is lazy. Being lazy,
let's do one more minute and we're going to
stretch it out more. Big shadows,
because the classes in the morning are so
long, because the morning is the best
time to think, and then they put you to
sleep. It doesn't matter, I'm a gum. So,
double drum, Titanic, let's go on such a
high trip. For the topic
of desire,
let's explore desire, what is
desire? Very well, you and I, on one, it's not as
sweet as humans.
If you see attractive things,
attractive things like money  What
would dollars be with a good answer?
I have a strong body because of me. You cry or
you say it will look
similar. Here it means a drink and
a
similar cappuccino and drink etc. Ten thousand
more things. When you see them, when you focus on
them, you don't want to
miss them. This
is my car. That is
my coffee. That is my $100 question
per answer.
This is my own. This is my yoga body. I don't want to
lose it.
This means I don't want to lose the
MBAs. This thought is a desire for
a question and an answer. I will give you a
break and if not, we will have to
continue without errors. Well, answer. I
will answer it because it needs a
break in Haikou. The highest school or the
lowest school.
Ward
Hariri, maybe
OK Series
Jr.
$100 because they are not bad
at being things. It is not Buddhism to say
people don't have good cappuccinos,
then they are Buddhists. Don't want to have
a yoga body, then you are Buddhists. I
never, ever enjoy money and
never buy a new car. Never
buy anything you enjoy.
That is Buddhism. Is
this a low
or high school? It is very, very, very, very low. Very,
very low. You feel that those Buddhists
in  Those paradises are avoiding
cappuccinos.
She has a smile
on her face. Look at this paradise of fruits,
and everything has meanings in the mirror.
Meaning. All the beautiful things
you can see are in a paradise of
moving desire. So if this is desire,
then this is a painting of the wheel
of life. Okay, if desire, if wanting
things is wrong, then you shouldn't
want the ability. You wanted to help
all the people. You shouldn't want to help all the
stars.
So Juan Jasso's answer
doesn't respond as often
as they come back to. Their answers are
better than just this. We're never joking, and
that's low school.
Definitely not our school.
You'd have to
add to it to make it our
school. What's wrong, you understand? It's wrong. It's bad to
have a Tesla. No, if everyone should have
one, then it's okay. Or do
you want a world without beautiful things? It's
the goal. Security is going to make sure that
everyone has nothing equal, and that's what
Buddhism is. See what I'm saying? They don't want
everyone to have an island and for there to be so many
roads and for everyone to be 100%
solar. Okay, that's what a body sadist
acquires. So  It's that you have to be careful
because he's teaching a good,
low definition of desire, and many times
in Asia, and in our
translations, we have the word "
ignorant"
because he desires a misunderstanding. It's rare,
so write
the ignorant desire for a $0
cappuccino.
Which is the intelligent one?
So share the intelligent desire.
Intelligent desire. There's nothing wrong with
intelligent desire.
I like cappuccino. I like it more than anything. Should I
give it to him? Are you crazy?
No, you're crazy. I do
n't understand where the cappuccino comes from.
I called the cappuccino so much that I'm going to make
sure everyone in the room
has one. I like suffering so much
that I'm going to make sure it's okay. So
let's take a 10-
minute break and come back
at 10:20.
Key
and stretch. I know what to do
to start. We have another half hour.
This is the longest half hour
because you're already tired, so be strong.
Be a little strong, inhabitant. I'll
be strong too.
Let's continue with this. Tomorrow,
if I have time, we're going to start the
review I'm doing of the 8
years we've done so far. That's right.
We're going to do half an hour each day
reviewing the retreats for those who didn't
attend, so this is an
opportunity to get all the
information.
Okay, very good. So, I
have an elderly person I care for, and once
a month I take
her out to dinner and to the movies. I
took her to the ballet last Sunday, and we
went to dinner. Let's
say she ate spaghetti. There are
two parts to the pasta:
the sauce and the pasta.
She always wears white clothes when we
go out. I don't know why, I don't know, when
you're 93 years old, you're not like, if
things fall off your fork, you spill something
and you don't even realize it. Thinking about it with me,
what was happening? So, there's a difference
between spaghetti and tomato sauce.
If you spill pasta on your
white pants after the ballet, it's not such a big
problem, you just wipe it off and it doesn't leave
much of a stain.
But if the spaghetti sauce spills
on your white pants, it can make
a stain.
And if there's a lot of olive oil, it
starts to spread. So, by the time we
got home, she
looked like she'd been in a war or
something, she was all red.  She was all red, I did
n't say anything, I just saw her clothes. They're like, just
some dust on your
pants and you can only get it off like that, you
can only get it off like
spaghetti without sauce. Jungle
is a difficult Tibetan word.
Jungle is very easy to remove, and
if I want you, very easy to remove. I already know,
but the desire, and the desire,
people to go ones and touch, it gets
relegated to slide.
It's like spaghetti sauce with too much
olive oil
and it's going to start spreading if you don't
clean it up quickly. It starts spreading,
a stain that will get bigger and bigger. It's
here, so it's the desire. There's
a little horse, it
has two qualities if you think about it.
Number one, the nature of not
sharing is that it gets worse. The person
who doesn't want to share, or doesn't want to, and
who doesn't want to share tomorrow, and it gets
bigger each time. First you don't want to
share, then you don't want to share
your car, then you don't want to
share your money, you can't share
your time, it gets worse and worse. It's like
olive oil, it spreads. The
habit of not sharing tends to grow,
it's a nature  The nature of
desire is different from other clichés,
and it's very difficult to remove from
the human mind. It's very difficult to
get it out of the mind, Villamanín.
There's a big topic in the world of
health and mind. It's
very interesting. It's very big. They have
a microphone so I can explain it for $0.
Fiscal, explain.
I want you to explain
in 5 minutes or 10, I don't mind. We'll take
a break. Doubt, a good
explanation, team. I'm
not going to speak slowly for the
translators.
Two minutes
with text. Yesterday we saw the different
schools of Buddhism
[Music],
and there are two big divisions: Hina. There is no
Mahayana anymore.
So, in terms of ways of seeing
things,
there are two things: Zampa.
Sampas means only, and that's the
first school.
That's the school that my text is about.
My text is
called "The Difficult Ficus Points
of the School of Only," written by
Jason Capa about a book written
by Jason Capa and commented on by another
author.
So, this word that says water
means difficult.
So, the School of Only
has eight mental functions, eight
consciousnesses. All the other schools
have six.
Someone in China would say the  eye, ear,
nose, taste,
then 6 and they are very famous in China and
India and Tibet but the school only
added two extra consciousnesses with yes
in union
then in yungas the same as English already so
in the school they only
have two extra consciousnesses for
where one is for where the seeds are kept
So
with this I give if it means like the funk
she calls the refrigerator conscience
is the place where all your
mental problems, all your players
are there like the plants,
like it happened. So my book
is about those two things.
It's what differentiates School
Only from the others.
So right now, where we are in the
book,
how do you achieve nirvana in School
Only? Which means no more
mental afflictions, no more crises.
If you have these two parts of your mind
that are intrinsic to
having those problems,
that's my face when I'm in class. My
book is very difficult,
so what will it be? Possibly, she thought it
was a poetic theme, but it's literal. It's
a very difficult book and a very difficult school
because what's the turn of the wheel?
School Only is the second.
So
Lord Wood, the first one, said all
the list of things, then he said what,
and after all these clarifications,
those,
and he had to do them because people
were confused.
So School Only is
completely fine, isn't it? Then he
had to say, well, some things are
empty, some things don't.
Some things come from your mind, other
things are as they are, and so on. So it gets
very technical and difficult,
and on top of that, he added two  Consciousness
to explain what happens to its seeds
when you do something and how
once
and then one of the things that
Buddhism deals with is how to reach
nirvana, how to end your
mental afflictions, okay, the ones that
are agitated, ansa jmg,
so this brings us to, yes,
these things that are supposedly part
of your head
and your conchi should be parts of your
mind like your eyes and your ability to
think,
so when you reach nirvana, when you get
rid of these,
you have to completely describe your
mind because those things are part of your
mind, or is it possible only like extracting them,
extracting their programs from your life like a
surgeon when he removes the tumor from a
cancer patient but leaves the
healthy tissue there, so the discussion is
when you become a leaf of a
lower school or a bodhisattva at the
level of the eighth level, which is an area
of ​​the highest school, what happens to your
mind? Does it destroy you, is it like a
lobotomy, like you remove your mind, or is it
possible that you just remove that and continue
without those problems? What is the answer
in life, arma, when you reach nirvana,
what happens to your mind
In the school of dwelling,
supposedly there is nirvana with residues,
nirvana without residues.
At Christmas, supposedly you disappear
completely when you remove all the
thanks, you disappear.
That's in the urban life weapon
and the higher schools. In other
words, when the surgeon removes the
tumor, he also removes the brain.
And then in the higher school,
supposedly in nirvana without residues, is
when you see emptiness directly.
You are not able to see anything but
emptiness. But after you leave
direct perception, then you have a
residue without residues, which means you still
have those frictions, you still have the
afflictions,
and a body, and everything. I think
the thing in the book is very interesting.
They say you have a seventh and an
eighth part of your mind. Only the
higher schools have these six
senses and your awareness of your six
senses, including your thinking.
But
the main school only says you have a
seventh and an eighth. The seventh is all
your thoughts, it's the bag of clichés, and they are
by Maite. And the eighth is the refrigerator
where you keep all your family,
the house, the refrigerator where,
because the school only says that
when your wife yells at you,
he's not outside.
Because all the perceptions in
school are just in fact
misunderstood and misinterpreted. They misperceive the
seeds that are blossoming from your
heart as external things when in
fact they are just seeds in your mind.
So if we go deeper than
hunger, if we go deeper, the reason you
have that church is because
you saw the refrigerator and didn't understand it.
Maybe that answers your question. In
school, I'll say it again, you
have two extra parts in your mind that we
call the sea, parts 7 and 8.
In schools,
other schools don't talk about that.
Number 7 represents all the
negative emotions from your classes. It's
the refrigerator.
When you talk about it, when you plant the
seed, that's why you yell at it. When you
yell at your children, last week
you put a seed in the refrigerator. And
when you yelled at your children, as if
consciously listening to your own
bad words, your own bad
words, it's not like someone wrote a
script and yelled at your children. What you
planted were the seeds that you
heard yourself say, and that planted a
seed in your mind. If you put the seeds
in the refrigerator, consciously or not,
last week, then this week
the seeds opened up. Where in  The
refrigerator,
the schools earlier, they say that the
seeds stream outside, the school
only says that the seed opened
in your own mind. Your husband is
yelling, is it properly you are watching a
video properly, okay, but what
excites me most about your text is that you know 7
Smith and the Sting, it is my misunderstanding
the eighth,
and perhaps that answers your question, the
6 and the 7, by understanding the 8, the churches
are possible if you understand
where your wife comes from in the
refrigerator, then that is the whole
process of deliverance will rest in the
school only the interaction between 7
and 8, the 7 is seeing the seeds
come out, in the 8 is thinking that the husband
is already in the kitchen and that he decided to
yell at you, okay, this is the school only
the version of the mind health sister
and it is very good, or it is not bad at all, I'm
going to say it again, you have a bag of
negative emotions in your mind
that are called the bag of
negative motions, then there is the Kun Si fan of
the school, the fundamental consciousness, the
refrigerator where all the
seeds live, last week yelling at
your children
and listening to yourself  You yelled, you put
a print on the refrigerator,
then at school, only that
you can stay out of nirvana and what
makes you angry is that number 7 doesn't
understand number 8, okay, number 7, the
video in his own mind, and thinks that the
young husband is yelling at you.
Now, what is the function of
Buddhist practice in school? Just someone
tell me, using 7 and 8,
what does the school want you to do
in this practice? How do you
destroy 7?
You only see what is happening in 8.
Then there is my husband, who didn't come
from him, the
minister, he just decided to visit me. That
is false, and that is maya. It is that illusion
that he didn't come from the room to the kitchen to
yell at me because he decided to. That is not what happened. What
really happened inside
number 8 is that a seed of yelling at the children
last week is opening in a
video in my own mind, and who put it
there? And I did it.
If you understand that you put it there,
could number 7 get angry? No, and that is
ignorance, like an animal among the
movement in school, only
ignorance, misunderstanding in the
School
salum in number 78 can only get
angry if number 7 number 7 can only get
angry if 7 I don't understand 8
and for 300 dollars I was going to say a thousand but I do
n't have that much I'm ready
pain to the question that it would be very
convenient if I forgot the question
already well
what is happening when what is the root
the seed behind the number 7 behind that
number 7
number 8
what is the question that someone is going to
ask you is very difficult that's why it's 300
dollars I'm going to say it again that it is
told in school only the anger
lives number 7 the imbalance lives in
number 7 number 7 test has been focused
opening the number 8 like the husband
yelling
the easy question is being is yelling
the wife in the kitchen is not yelling
is inside the number 8 that now the
question for word for 300 dollars so much
total
and remember
and I will remember it because the 7 thinks that the
number 8 is outside
sign because the 7 thinks that
because the number 7 has a core where
the minds come the frictions
mental and number 7 thinks that
number 8 is actually outside
300 dollars. What I want to do is
stop being clear before
and I'm going to ask a question that doesn't deserve
300 dollars
because according to the school, it just
tells me it feels like it's late. What's
in is out because in
school, it's just one of the
big questions of school, it
just created the misunderstanding, so
because it feels like the husband is
out when he's really in your
own mind. Nice, yes, yes, it has maybe
close
yesterday, sure,
Charles, life times of the world outside,
for countless lives of the word
outside,
and there's a special seed in school
just
for countless stable lives, talked to
your friends about your husband being
there, and because of that talk, for
countless lives, you have middle class in your
mind that makes you feel like your husband
is already out when he's really in
your mind, and that's school just, it's
here.
Blatter
is a very certified system and it's very
good, very good, if you really
understand. School just increases, it's
very good, and because we're talking about
success, if we were on the topic  With
white pants and spaghetti, we were
on the topic of why he has
white pants. I don't know,
Yukawa, it's
that oil stain. It has two
qualities. Number one, it tends to
spread.
Once you take refuge in someone who doesn't want to
share a cup of coffee, you're not going to be left out. You're
not going to want
people to stay home, and so
the oil stain grows. Sometimes, not
sharing, it tends to spread. And what is
the second quality? It's very difficult to
remove.
You should see his white pants;
patterns of bread are already appearing
on the sides, the sides, and the sides, but
something stays, something stays there, the little stain. Yes, I
think if we put
black spots on it, like tiger stripes, then they're going to be
really
difficult to remove, and that's why we
went to the Word document.
Because when you remove that tumor, you remove the
tumor, you remove the brain, and it can surpass
a human being and remove the number 7 and
not kill them.
Is it possible to completely remove the spaghetti
from the white pants?
Should the pants be burned? That's the
question that we then went to
school for. And come back, he has a
question.
Don't argue anymore. The school only
says that the school says that you should
Burn the pants, otherwise there won't
be a Michael after the MNR, humanity
will disappear
since this is a very big topic, they are
layers
and I'll say it again because Phil said
all the clichés are misunderstandings
and we're going to talk about that, it's a very
big topic this week,
let me say another thing about consciousness
7, which I hardly ever mentioned, consciousness 7, more
just save arrows, save all the
minds, lessons and other mental functions,
almost all of them are in the number 7, so it
destroys the 7 of stars, the whole mind,
that's the question, it's called the
arrow consciousness but it's not 100% crisis, it's
like 80 percent other thoughts, it's
something that there isn't a list of them
when the one
who thinks there is is
n't very big, so that
takes us to the next one, and they
directed, and what is the end of master or
not
for this, what is the image
if the guy has spaghetti in his shirt
from number 3, okay, let's meditate on
that, you have to burn the shirt, you can
remove your misunderstanding without destroying
the mind, okay,
17 Conway
Ching
about Walmart eating
But I'm going to say it again, and I want an
intelligent comment about
this from someone who aborted us.
Export
poetry standards are always here; it's always like this
with that regime, the sector of
truth.
Although, why am I talking about this?
Because if you're a translator, you have to
read the poetry. That means it's
coming from another book, that it's quoting
something. Well, what it said, but you know, from the
music, from the Tibetan beat, that it
took it from another book. 'In it, it says, "Who
cares? I do
n't want to go to that other book," it says, and
find out what else it said. That's why
our translations are so slow and
our classes are so lame. Wouldn't it be
good to find a poem and listen to the whole thing? Maybe there's
something
good there. We should have this habit:
when you see a quote, go read the
book. So I went and read it, and then
here I have it for you. And I'll tell you
something interesting: it's
from a poem by The
Diamond Way. Make your jacket from your cellar. You
are the paradise of the lower half.
Can you be closer to paradise than the middle
of the beach in the middle of Kleia? Okay, that
whitmill, which means see if the verse is
directed to Ching.  wan r if you are
incarnated in the prison of suffering
due to using witness class
your desire for English you are already chained
in samsara and by the oil stain that
sells 6 for not sharing what you have
for not wanting to share what one day you will not even
distinguish it would not be interesting to see the
other three lines
and we can do this because of the great
work of John Brady who is not here
because there is such a version
and it is because not because of what has taken us
years to get here as this
book search tool we
are already talking about being able to
search five million odd pages
in sounds
here goes the whole verse
of Guadiana the path of the claimant and
that I was thinking because he made that I
was thinking that he made this condition
of deaf Wenger
the actions
the sword of anger murder
higher rebirth because already because it
kills your tools positive seeds
the sword weak already but not with climate
of positive seeds of people and the
wives of the stain say baguette and
of the desire to chain the unleashed pressure
and the river of your karma takes you to the ocean
of pain
nothing that has a word
and when you get there the waves that you want
that  I want you to
age, you have problems, chronic pain,
tsunami, the chronic tsunami called life, the one who
is burdened by karma, which
is created by anger and desire. That's the
whole poem, and the poem is
teaching cause and effect.
It says how arrows create karma, which
is an important topic that we're going to see
these weeks. English, there are no karmas, okay,
racing, you can't collect, let's go back
to the page. Only who wants to
explain that place
wants to explain that if English, there is no
karma for school, only you have
the husbands in your head,
so you're not going to yell back
at school, only in
apartment 7 of your mind, understand
apartment 8 of your mind.
So apartment 7 is going to see that
8 is just yelling and the husband, but
the husband didn't decide to yell, the husband
comes from me,
so apartment 7 can't get
wet with 8,
so apartment 27 isn't going to
answer the husband and it's not going to be
new karma, okay, Franz Kafka question,
but not equally
connected,
what?
[Music]
Back,
good here
without me,
drone with nothing
in its path
[Music]
was a mandala guru
would say
yes
be kind
he is good
white
and triumph
[Music] they are
very brave to come here to
sit for three hours nobody in the
world area to be more than that are they
crazy or are they special